And one of the
questions they asked one
of the is you
if you could ask
the aliens any one
question what would it
be And one of
the characters says I
would ask how did
you do it How
did you manage to
get through this technological
adolescence without destroying yourselves
How did you make
it through And ever
since I saw it
it like 20 years
ago I think I
saw that movie it's
kind of with me
And that's the frame
that I use is
that you know we
are knocking on the
of these incredible capabilities
right The ability to
basically machines out of
right I think it
was inevitable that the
instant we started working
with fire
but how we handle
it is not inevitable
And so I think
the next few years
we're going to be
with you how do
we keep these systems
under control that are
highly autonomous and smarter
than any human